<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<lansuite>
	<header>
		<filetype>LanSuite</filetype>
		<version>2.0</version>
		<source>http://www.lansuite.de</source>
		<date>2010-01-02 05:47</date>
	</header>
	<table>
		<table_head>
			<name>translation</name>
		</table_head>
		<content>
			<entry>
				<id>82e266c2029974fe3e5a853d2d884cec</id>
				<org>Nickname eintragen</org>
				<en>Enter Nickname</en>
				<es>Introduzca Nickname</es>
				<fr>Entrez Pseudo</fr>
				<nl>Voer Nickname</nl>
				<it>Inserisci Nickname</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>58e62b3f8cbbe2cf014f88b4323280ec</id>
				<org>Konnte nicht zum Server verbinden, da du kein Nickname eingetragen hast</org>
				<en>Could not connect to the server, because you have registered no nickname</en>
				<es>No se pudo conectar con el servidor, ya que se ha registrado ningún apodo</es>
				<fr>Impossible de se connecter au serveur, parce que vous avez enregistré aucune pseudo</fr>
				<nl>Kon niet verbinden met de server, omdat je geen nickname hebt geregistreerd</nl>
				<it>Impossibile connettersi al server, perché ti sei registrato no nickname</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>05b8ce1af5b41b0d1866743d25a6575f</id>
				<org>Teamspeak Server Passwort eintragen für</org>
				<en>Teamspeak server password to enter for</en>
				<es>Contraseña del servidor de Teamspeak para entrar a</es>
				<fr>Mot de passe serveur Teamspeak à pénétrer pour</fr>
				<nl>Teamspeak server wachtwoord in te voeren voor</nl>
				<it>Password del server Teamspeak per entrare per la</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>4fbc64274d15cb81b996ce63e6ddcedf</id>
				<org>Konnte nicht zum Server verbinden, da du kein Teamspeak Server Passwort eingetragen hast</org>
				<en>Could not connect to the server, because you have not registered TeamSpeak Server Password</en>
				<es>No se pudo conectar con el servidor, ya que no se ha registrado TeamSpeak Server Contraseña</es>
				<fr>Impossible de se connecter au serveur, parce que vous n&amp;#39;êtes pas encore inscrit Mot de passe TeamSpeak Server</fr>
				<nl>Kon niet verbinden met de server, omdat je niet hebt TeamSpeak Server Wachtwoord geregistreerd</nl>
				<it>Impossibile connettersi al server, perché non avete registrato TeamSpeak Server Password</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>81e42920b94e166aac04484c029a2bcc</id>
				<org>Channel Passwort eintragen für</org>
				<en>Channel password to enter for</en>
				<es>Canal contraseña para entrar a</es>
				<fr>Channel mot de passe à entrer pour</fr>
				<nl>Kanaal wachtwoord in te voeren voor</nl>
				<it>Canale password per entrare per la</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5c68f3801a25f1ae644a0ab9eb99721a</id>
				<org>Konnte nicht zum Server verbinden, da du kein Channel Passwort eingetragen hast</org>
				<en>Could not connect to the server, because you have entered no channel</en>
				<es>No se pudo conectar con el servidor, ya que han entrado en ningún canal</es>
				<fr>Impossible de se connecter au serveur, parce que vous avez entré aucun canal</fr>
				<nl>Kon niet verbinden met de server, omdat je geen kanaal heeft ingevoerd</nl>
				<it>Impossibile connettersi al server, perché avete inserito nessun canale</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>50287fc12e1f89d8549b65b07c831d31</id>
				<org>Kein Teamspeak Server konfiguriert.</org>
				<en>No TeamSpeak server configured.</en>
				<es>No hay ningún servidor TeamSpeak configurado.</es>
				<fr>Aucun serveur TeamSpeak configuré.</fr>
				<nl>Geen TeamSpeak server geconfigureerd.</nl>
				<it>Nessun server TeamSpeak configurato.</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>22f8fec819121753239cc7d94cdbfe85</id>
				<org>Übersicht der Channels und User auf dem TeamSpeak Server. Um auf den Server zu connecten, einfach auf einen Channel klicken und den Anweisungen folgen.</org>
				<en>Overview of the channels and users on the TeamSpeak server. To connect to the server, simply click on a channel and follow the instructions.</en>
				<es>Vista general de los canales y los usuarios en el servidor de TeamSpeak. Para conectar con el servidor, basta con hacer clic en un canal y siga las instrucciones.</es>
				<fr>Vue d&amp;#39;ensemble sur les canaux et les utilisateurs sur le serveur TeamSpeak. Pour vous connecter au serveur, vous n&amp;#39;avez qu&amp;#39;à cliquer sur un canal et suivez les instructions.</fr>
				<nl>Overzicht van de kanalen en gebruikers op de TeamSpeak server. Om verbinding met de server, klikt u op een kanaal en volg de instructies.</nl>
				<it>Panoramica dei canali e degli utenti sul server di TeamSpeak. Per connettersi al server, è sufficiente fare clic su un canale e seguire le istruzioni.</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>8faa77c9cf7465efb7d16af6a0b2630c</id>
				<org>AUS</org>
				<en>OFF</en>
				<es>OFF</es>
				<fr>OFF</fr>
				<nl>OFF</nl>
				<it>OFF</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>2958e457c4bceb5786345e5e2d7817fe</id>
				<org>Aktivieren</org>
				<en>Enable</en>
				<es>Posibilitar</es>
				<fr>Activer</fr>
				<nl>In staat stellen</nl>
				<it>Consentire</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>d9681d05860552e9c3113da381f916fc</id>
				<org>AN</org>
				<en>AN</en>
				<es>AN</es>
				<fr>AN</fr>
				<nl>AN</nl>
				<it>AN</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5e3e07837e609be93787d022ed8c52ab</id>
				<org>Deaktivieren</org>
				<en>Disable</en>
				<es>Desactivar</es>
				<fr>Désactiver</fr>
				<nl>Uitschakelen</nl>
				<it>Disattivare</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>7257c31fe2f87a7eaf54c0cea3e2c234</id>
				<org>Teamspeak Server Passwort eintragen für</org>
				<en>Teamspeak Server Password adding fr</en>
				<es>TeamSpeak Server Contraseña fr añadir</es>
				<fr>TeamSpeak Server passe en ajoutant</fr>
				<nl>Teamspeak Server Wachtwoord toevoegen fr</nl>
				<it>TeamSpeak Server Password fr aggiungendo</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5a781160e44f1875982d9451f8b08bed</id>
				<org>Channel Passwort eintragen für</org>
				<en>Channel Register Forgot fr</en>
				<es>Canal Registro ¿Olvidaste tu fr</es>
				<fr>Channel S&amp;#39;enregistrer J&amp;#39;ai oublié mon fr</fr>
				<nl>Kanaal Registreren Wachtwoord fr</nl>
				<it>Channel Register Forgot fr</it>
				<file>teamspeak2</file>
			</entry>
		</content>
	</table>
</lansuite>
