<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<lansuite>
	<header>
		<filetype>LanSuite</filetype>
		<version>2.0</version>
		<source>http://www.lansuite.de</source>
		<date>2010-01-02 05:47</date>
	</header>
	<table>
		<table_head>
			<name>translation</name>
		</table_head>
		<content>
			<entry>
				<id>7163118c683013bd76207da5ef80f9e8</id>
				<org>Du hast in der letzten Minute bereits 5 mal dein Passwort falsch eingegeben. Bitte warte einen Moment, bevor du es erneut versuchen darfst</org>
				<en>In the last Minute you have entered 5 times a wrong password. Please wait a moment before you can try again.</en>
				<es>Se han introducido correctamente en el último minuto como 5 veces su contraseña. Por favor, tuvo un momento antes de poder volver a intentarlo</es>
				<fr>Ils ont été mal saisis dans la dernière minute que 5 fois votre mot de passe. S&amp;#39;il vous plaît Soyez eu un moment avant que vous soyez autorisé à essayer de nouveau</fr>
				<nl>Ze zijn ten onrechte opgenomen in de laatste minuut als 5 keer uw wachtwoord. Please Be had een moment voordat je mag het opnieuw te proberen</nl>
				<it>Sono stati inseriti correttamente nel minuto finale 5 volte la tua password. Si prega di essere avuto un attimo prima di essere autorizzati a riprova</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>96cd67b7c7fdd4ba1e0a82a3825dda2a</id>
				<org>Dieser Benutzer existiert nicht in unserer Datenbank. Bitte prüfe die eingegebene Email/ID</org>
				<en>This user doesen't exist in the Database. Pleas check your entered Email/ID</en>
				<es>Este usuario no existe en nuestra base de datos. Por favor, consulte la entrada de correo electrónico / ID</es>
				<fr>Cet utilisateur n&amp;#39;existe pas dans notre base de données. S&amp;#39;il vous plaît vérifier l&amp;#39;entrée e-mail / ID</fr>
				<nl>Deze gebruiker bestaat niet in onze database. Controleer de ingevoerde e-mail / ID</nl>
				<it>Questo utente non esiste nel nostro database. Si prega di verificare le iscritte e-mail / ID</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>18da9c0f07f1c38279a2590c3d75c3bf</id>
				<org>Login fehlgeschlagen. Email (%1) nicht verifiziert</org>
				<en>Login failed. Email (%1) not verified.</en>
				<es>De acceso fallidos. E (%1) no verificado</es>
				<fr>Échec de la connexion. E (%1) non vérifié</fr>
				<nl>Login failed. E (%1) niet gecontroleerd</nl>
				<it>Login failed. E (1%) non verificato</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>effcc817fc18787f96bc0b665b8faa8e</id>
				<org>Die von dir eingebenen Login-Daten sind fehlerhaft. Bitte überprüfe die Eingaben.</org>
				<en>Your Logindata are wrong. Pleas check your entrys</en>
				<es>Cados por que la información de acceso es incorrecta. Por favor, compruebe sus entradas.</es>
				<fr>Gistrée par vous les informations de connexion est incorrect. S&amp;#39;il vous plaît vérifier vos entrées.</fr>
				<nl>Streerd door u de login informatie is onjuist. Please check your items.</nl>
				<it>Registrato da voi le informazioni di login non è corretto. Si prega di controllare le voci.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>ae9da221e6553e31803344d27f2e81a8</id>
				<org>Du bist nicht eingecheckt. Im Intranetmodus ist ein Einloggen nur möglich, wenn du eingecheckt bist.</org>
				<en>You are not checked in. In the intranet mode, a login is only possible if you are checked in.</en>
				<es>No se comprueban. En el modo de intranet, un inicio de sesión sólo es posible si se chequea.</es>
				<fr>Ils ne sont pas vérifiées. Dans le mode intranet, un code d&amp;#39;accès n&amp;#39;est possible que si vous êtes enregistrés.</fr>
				<nl>Ze zijn niet gecontroleerd. In het intranet-modus, een login is alleen mogelijk als u worden gecontroleerd.</nl>
				<it>Essi non vengono controllate. Nella modalità intranet, un account di accesso è possibile solo se si è verificata.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>6217b75cb76719dfb767ba9e87e62082</id>
				<org>Bitte melde dich bei der Organisation.</org>
				<en>Please get in touch with the organization.</en>
				<es>Por favor, póngase en contacto con la organización.</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît prendre contact avec l&amp;#39;organisation.</fr>
				<nl>Neem contact op met de organisatie.</nl>
				<it>Si prega di mettersi in contatto con l&amp;#39;organizzazione.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>45df15e01082967b782698c0a4c42e75</id>
				<org>Du bist bereits ausgecheckt. Im Intranetmodus ist ein Einloggen nur möglich, wenn du eingecheckt bist.</org>
				<en>You are already checked out. In the intranet mode, a login is only possible if you are checked in.</en>
				<es>Usted ya está desprotegido. En el modo de intranet, un inicio de sesión sólo es posible si se chequea.</es>
				<fr>Vous êtes déjà extrait. Dans le mode intranet, un code d&amp;#39;accès n&amp;#39;est possible que si vous êtes enregistrés.</fr>
				<nl>U bent al uitgecheckt. In het intranet-modus, een login is alleen mogelijk als u worden gecontroleerd.</nl>
				<it>Sei già estratto. Nella modalità intranet, un account di accesso è possibile solo se si è verificata.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>07834f918b2652509fbcae60694b9a58</id>
				<org>Erfolgreich eingeloggt. Die Änderungen werden beim Laden der nächsten Seite wirksam.</org>
				<en>Successfully logged in. The changes will take effect when the next page is loaded.</en>
				<es>Has cerrado correctamente. Los cambios surtirán efecto cuando la página siguiente a la carga.</es>
				<fr>Connecté avec succès. Les modifications prendront effet dès la prochaine page à charger.</fr>
				<nl>Succesvol aangemeld. De wijzigingen worden van kracht wanneer de volgende pagina te laden.</nl>
				<it>Successo registrato. Le modifiche entreranno in vigore quando la pagina successiva per caricare.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>f07ec1b01555ed1939e25db154cc4450</id>
				<org>Am</org>
				<en>At</en>
				<es>Encendido</es>
				<fr>Sur</fr>
				<nl>Aan</nl>
				<it>Su</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>d57f0b8306324a0f0cb2d5f4613155e4</id>
				<org>Fehlerhafte Logins</org>
				<en>Loginfaults</en>
				<es>Intentos de conexión fallidos</es>
				<fr>Les connexions échouées</fr>
				<nl>Failed Logins</nl>
				<it>Failed Logins</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>d309c908a40bb081c8b380d6806e42f1</id>
				<org>Es wurden fehlerhafte Logins seit deinem letzten erfolgreichen Login durchgeführt.</org>
				<en>There have been incorrect logins since your last successful login.</en>
				<es>Ha habido inicios de sesión incorrecta, ya que su último acceso logrado.</es>
				<fr>Il ya eu des connexions incorrectes depuis votre dernière connexion réussie.</fr>
				<nl>Er zijn onjuiste logins sinds uw laatste geslaagde login.</nl>
				<it>Ci sono state login errata, poiché l&amp;#39;ultimo accesso riuscito.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>0f708c0c9ae26b1978ac5107c98a7450</id>
				<org>Keine Userid beim Login via Cookie erkannt.</org>
				<en>No user ID detected at login via cookie.</en>
				<es>N º ID de usuario al iniciar sesión detectado a través de cookies.</es>
				<fr>Aucune ID d&amp;#39;utilisateur lors de la connexion détectée par l&amp;#39;intermédiaire de cookies.</fr>
				<nl>Geen gebruikers-ID bij het inloggen gedetecteerd via Cookie.</nl>
				<it>N. ID utente quando si accede rilevati tramite cookie.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c58d5b774ad43337ac373b8518d88b4b</id>
				<org>Kein Uniquekey beim Login via Cookie erkannt.</org>
				<en>No Uniquekey recognized at login via cookie.</en>
				<es>N Uniquekey reconoció al iniciar la sesión a través de cookies.</es>
				<fr>N Uniquekey reconnu lors de la connexion par l&amp;#39;intermédiaire de cookies.</fr>
				<nl>Geen Uniquekey herkend bij het inloggen via cookie.</nl>
				<it>N. Uniquekey riconosciuti al momento del login tramite cookie.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>8fb0bcc0b38db9274e73487e07642c1c</id>
				<org>Du wurdest erfolgreich ausgeloggt. Vielen dank für deinen Besuch.</org>
				<en>You have successfully logged out. Thank you for your visit.</en>
				<es>Ha cerrado la sesión. Gracias por su visita.</es>
				<fr>Vous êtes déconnecté. Nous vous remercions de votre visite.</fr>
				<nl>U hebt met succes uitgelogd. Dank u voor uw bezoek.</nl>
				<it>Hai correttamente disconnesso. Grazie per la vostra visita.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>0ca72d08a148324a5fd451bb77d36c5d</id>
				<org>Benutzerwechsel erfolgreich. Die Änderungen werden beim laden der nächsten Seite wirksam.</org>
				<en>Users change successful. The changes will take effect when the next page is loaded.</en>
				<es>Usuarios de cambio con éxito. Los cambios surtirán efecto cuando la página siguiente a la carga.</es>
				<fr>Utilisateurs changement réussi. Les modifications prendront effet dès la prochaine page à charger.</fr>
				<nl>Gebruikers verandering succesvol. De wijzigingen worden van kracht wanneer de volgende pagina te laden.</nl>
				<it>Agli utenti di modificare successo. Le modifiche entreranno in vigore quando la pagina successiva per caricare.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>39f5e954cb57ce0e3796b7ae82d61260</id>
				<org>Dein Benutzerlevel ist geringer, als das des Ziel-Benutzers. Ein Wechsel ist daher untersagt</org>
				<en>Your user level is lower than that of the target user. A change is therefore prohibited</en>
				<es>Su nivel de usuario es inferior a la del usuario de destino. Un cambio es por tanto, prohibida</es>
				<fr>Votre niveau de l&amp;#39;utilisateur est inférieur à celui de l&amp;#39;utilisateur cible. Un changement est donc interdit</fr>
				<nl>Uw gebruikersnaam niveau is lager dan dat van de beoogde gebruiker. Een verandering is dus verboden</nl>
				<it>Il livello di utente è inferiore a quello degli utenti target. Un cambiamento è pertanto vietata</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>b7fbf2ca145b288118026b338f79ad64</id>
				<org>Fehler: Falscher switch back code! Das kann daran liegen, dass dein Browser keine Cookies unterstützt.</org>
				<en>Error: Wrong switchback code! This may be because your browser does not support cookies.</en>
				<es>Error: Código de zigzag ¡Incorrecto! Esto puede ser porque su navegador no soporta cookies.</es>
				<fr>Erreur: code Switchback Faux! Cette mai-être parce que votre navigateur ne supporte pas les cookies.</fr>
				<nl>Fout: Verkeerde Switchback code! Dit kan zijn omdat uw browser geen cookies ondersteunt.</nl>
				<it>Errore: switchback codice errato! Questo può essere perché il tuo browser non supporta i cookie.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c9c677f6dbdf02b8a074626ebe223fb9</id>
				<org>Fehler: Keine Switchbackdaten gefunden! Das kann daran liegen, dass dein Browser keine Cookies unterstützt.</org>
				<en>Error: No Switchback data found! This may be because your browser does not support cookies.</en>
				<es>Error: No hay datos Switchback encontrado! Esto puede ser porque su navegador no soporta cookies.</es>
				<fr>Erreur: Aucune donnée Switchback trouvé! Cette mai-être parce que votre navigateur ne supporte pas les cookies.</fr>
				<nl>Fout: geen Switchback gegevens gevonden! Dit kan zijn omdat uw browser geen cookies ondersteunt.</nl>
				<it>Errore: Nessun dato Switchback trovato! Questo può essere perché il tuo browser non supporta i cookie.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>a50d91f23c4f9cb8ee1d81d93d03e7ff</id>
				<org>Vorschau</org>
				<en>Preview</en>
				<es>Prevista</es>
				<fr>Preview</fr>
				<nl>Preview</nl>
				<it>Anteprima</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>8b14d55bb9668ee40cde8f17314feb15</id>
				<org>Fett</org>
				<en>Fat</en>
				<es>Gordo</es>
				<fr>Graisse</fr>
				<nl>Vet</nl>
				<it>Grasso</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>77778d8c610270cab20769b2d0131b7a</id>
				<org>Kursiv</org>
				<en>Italic</en>
				<es>Itálica</es>
				<fr>Italique</fr>
				<nl>Schuin</nl>
				<it>Corsivo</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>a5e5b758bd63de72993cc13cb5a824dd</id>
				<org>Unterstrichen</org>
				<en>Unterline</en>
				<es>Subrayado</es>
				<fr>Souligné</fr>
				<nl>Onderstrepen</nl>
				<it>Sottolineato</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5ea1018a4819fe3436d4c4ffdedaaede</id>
				<org>Durchstreichen</org>
				<en>Strike</en>
				<es>Tachado</es>
				<fr>Barré</fr>
				<nl>Doorhalen</nl>
				<it>Strikeout</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>d86a346284e5d71226e722aecec81be9</id>
				<org>Tiefstellen</org>
				<en>Low points</en>
				<es>Subíndice</es>
				<fr>Indice</fr>
				<nl>Subscript</nl>
				<it>Pedice</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e1db333cb7742e9b6dcdb152521c8fd8</id>
				<org>Hochstellen</org>
				<en>High points</en>
				<es>Superíndice</es>
				<fr>Exposant</fr>
				<nl>Superscript</nl>
				<it>Apice</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>ca0dbad92a874b2f69b549293387925e</id>
				<org>Code</org>
				<en>Code</en>
				<es>Código</es>
				<fr>Code</fr>
				<nl>Code</nl>
				<it>Codice</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>0da3b78d9546e8fe0065cd3c9ed1879a</id>
				<org>Bild</org>
				<en>Picture</en>
				<es>Cuadro</es>
				<fr>Image</fr>
				<nl>Film</nl>
				<it>Immagine</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>429bdf7fb1ab9dd6ff5f8f5b6d380968</id>
				<org>Zurück</org>
				<en>Back</en>
				<es>Espalda</es>
				<fr>Retour</fr>
				<nl>Terug</nl>
				<it>Indietro</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>27e0c320ea995df1ae1be0dd00ae9c06</id>
				<org>Angehängte Datei herunterladen</org>
				<en>Download Attached file</en>
				<es>Descarga de archivos adjuntos</es>
				<fr>Attached File Download</fr>
				<nl>Bijgevoegde bestand</nl>
				<it>Scarica il file in allegato</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5f4110486d00f1ceafd93d33f82c55a8</id>
				<org>Hinzufügen</org>
				<en>Add</en>
				<es>Agregar</es>
				<fr>Ajouter</fr>
				<nl>Toevoegen</nl>
				<it>Aggiungere</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>59b0fe8d3fee044fb03d40984e6300ed</id>
				<org>Ändern</org>
				<en>Change</en>
				<es>Cambiar</es>
				<fr>Changer</fr>
				<nl>Veranderen</nl>
				<it>Cambiare</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>cce55fad709e2b8a964dc43dcf1bd6bc</id>
				<org>Editieren</org>
				<en>Edit</en>
				<es>Editar</es>
				<fr>Modifier</fr>
				<nl>Edit</nl>
				<it>Modifica</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>1010b01ca33474b21dfca7411a13552c</id>
				<org>Löschen</org>
				<en>Delete</en>
				<es>Borrar</es>
				<fr>Supprimer</fr>
				<nl>Wissen</nl>
				<it>Eliminare</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c10dbfd82ada39d491ee13697ce3034b</id>
				<org>Senden</org>
				<en>Send</en>
				<es>Enviar</es>
				<fr>Envoyer</fr>
				<nl>Sturen</nl>
				<it>Inviare</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5acc175c727c1cbe58d20e711edc2bf3</id>
				<org>Benutzerdetails aufrufen</org>
				<en>Show Userdetails</en>
				<es>Ver los detalles de usuario</es>
				<fr>Voir Détails de l&amp;#39;utilisateur</fr>
				<nl>View User Details</nl>
				<it>View User Details</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5393323c3710c96ed0313b77bb70c02e</id>
				<org>Bitte wähle eine Möglichkeit aus:</org>
				<en>Please select one possibility:</en>
				<es>Por favor seleccione una opción:</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît sélectionnez une option:</fr>
				<nl>Selecteer een optie:</nl>
				<it>Si prega di selezionare un&amp;#39;opzione:</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>32036005d1f6ed59803ba3e13c80993e</id>
				<org>Avatar</org>
				<en>Avatar</en>
				<es>Avatar</es>
				<fr>Avatar</fr>
				<nl>Avatar</nl>
				<it>Avatar</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>0aa7015fbee329464981c3654f3119fd</id>
				<org>Gast</org>
				<en>Guest</en>
				<es>Anónimo</es>
				<fr>Client</fr>
				<nl>Guest</nl>
				<it>Guest</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>25ae1ec0eccec4f159ae670451e41f95</id>
				<org>Kommentare</org>
				<en>Comments</en>
				<es>Comentarios</es>
				<fr>Commentaires</fr>
				<nl>Reacties</nl>
				<it>Commenti</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c52aebc06becfffc14adc9444121379a</id>
				<org>Zitieren</org>
				<en>Citations</en>
				<es>Citar</es>
				<fr>Citer</fr>
				<nl>Citeren</nl>
				<it>Citare</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>ab559eb6c85d0c3a970dca3e9a94312c</id>
				<org>Bitte logge dich ein, bevor du einen Kommentar verfasst</org>
				<en>Please log in before you leave a comment</en>
				<es>Debes iniciar sesión antes de dejar un comentario</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît vous connecter avant de laisser un commentaire</fr>
				<nl>Gelieve in te loggen voordat u een reactie achterlaten</nl>
				<it>Accedi prima di lasciare un commento</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>cd05591e8d0d62d2c11ba7421d80cdba</id>
				<org>Kommentar</org>
				<en>Comment</en>
				<es>Comentario</es>
				<fr>Commentaire</fr>
				<nl>Reactie</nl>
				<it>Commento</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>03ec70e16109a01b4badf461cc3cfea9</id>
				<org>Es gibt einen neuen Kommentar</org>
				<en>There is a new comment</en>
				<es>Hay un comentario nuevo</es>
				<fr>Il ya un nouveau commentaire</fr>
				<nl>Er is een nieuwe reactie</nl>
				<it>C&amp;#39;è un nuovo commento</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>50ee067f8b85c79972405065148940bb</id>
				<org>Es wurde ein neuer Kommentar in einem Lansuite-Modul geschrieben: %URL%</org>
				<en>It was written a new comment in a Lansuite module: %URL%</en>
				<es>Fue escrito un nuevo comentario en un módulo de Lansuite:%URL%</es>
				<fr>Il a été écrit un nouveau commentaire dans un module Lansuite:%URL%</fr>
				<nl>Het werd geschreven een nieuw bericht in een Lansuite module:%URL%</nl>
				<it>E &amp;#39;stato scritto un nuovo commento in un modulo Lansuite:%%URL</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>edac91e982f98f2f8bc845e59defdf73</id>
				<org>Du bist nicht berechtigt, diesen Kommentar zu editieren</org>
				<en>You are not authorized to edit this comment</en>
				<es>Usted no está autorizado a editar este comentario</es>
				<fr>Vous n&amp;#39;êtes pas autorisé à modifier ce commentaire</fr>
				<nl>U bent niet gemachtigd om te bewerken dit commentaar</nl>
				<it>Non sei autorizzato a modificare questo commento</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>423e555c5ec3885f2bb5d9d2d6627f63</id>
				<org>Monitoring</org>
				<en>Monitoring</en>
				<es>Seguimiento</es>
				<fr>Surveillance</fr>
				<nl>Monitoring</nl>
				<it>Monitoraggio</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5b01db7abd9df1cb5cd68516973816cd</id>
				<org>Lesezeichen</org>
				<en>Bookmark</en>
				<es>Marcadores</es>
				<fr>Signets</fr>
				<nl>Bookmarks</nl>
				<it>Bookmarks</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>daef98f1581fb82c6942443d98560b59</id>
				<org>Diesen Beitrag in meine Lesezeichen aufnehmen&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Lesezeichen ist Vorraussetzung, um Benachrichtigung per Mail zu abonnieren)&lt;/i&gt;</org>
				<en>Add this entry in my bookmarks &amp;lt;br&amp;gt; &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;(Bookmark is a prerequisite to subscribe to receive by mail)&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt;</en>
				<es>Añadir esta entrada en mis marcadores &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Marcador es un requisito previo para suscribirse para recibir por correo electrónico)&lt;/i&gt;</es>
				<fr>Ajouter cette rubrique à mes favoris &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Bookmark est une condition de s&amp;#39;abonner pour recevoir par mail)&lt;/i&gt;</fr>
				<nl>Voeg dit item in mijn bladwijzers &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Bookmark is een voorwaarde om je te abonneren te ontvangen per post)&lt;/i&gt;</nl>
				<it>Aggiungere questa voce nei miei bookmarks &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;(Segnalibro è un prerequisito per iscriversi per ricevere via mail)&lt;/i&gt;</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>50c6a2e17e1d241b1b84acfd442f3751</id>
				<org>E-Mail Benachrichtigung</org>
				<en>E-mail alerts</en>
				<es>E-mail alerts</es>
				<fr>E-mail alertes</fr>
				<nl>E-mail alerts</nl>
				<it>E-mail avvisi</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>f8a934dee2aa489c6aacd63e349073ee</id>
				<org>Bei Antworten auf diesen Beitrag eine Internet-Mail an mich senden</org>
				<en>When sending replies to this post, send me an email</en>
				<es>Al enviar las respuestas a este post es un correo de Internet a mí</es>
				<fr>Lors de l&amp;#39;envoi des réponses à ce poste est une messagerie Internet à moi</fr>
				<nl>Wanneer het verzenden van de antwoorden op deze post is een internet-mail naar mij</nl>
				<it>Quando si inviano le risposte a questo post è un messaggio di posta Internet per me</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>ba74299214c2bb9652a50a9fa7a49e89</id>
				<org>System-E-Mail</org>
				<en>System email</en>
				<es>E-Mail System</es>
				<fr>E-Mail System</fr>
				<nl>E-mailsysteem</nl>
				<it>E-Mail System</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>7345f3bbcfb48bfd6581d8d8b7d05859</id>
				<org>Bei Antworten auf diesen Beitrag eine System-Mail an mich senden</org>
				<en>On replies to this post send a system mail to me</en>
				<es>Enviar las respuestas a esta entrada a un sistema electrónico que me</es>
				<fr>Envoyez les réponses à ce poste à un système-Mail to me</fr>
				<nl>Stuur de antwoorden naar dit bericht aan een systeem-mail mij</nl>
				<it>Inviare le risposte a questo post a un sistema-Mail to me</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>bd9a11a632f2f4c3d0f68829fe8feca2</id>
				<org>Eintrag #%1 aus Tabelle &quot;%2&quot; gelöscht</org>
				<en>Entry #%1 of table &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; deleted</en>
				<es>Entrada #%1 de la tabla &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; suprimido</es>
				<fr>Entrée #%1 du tableau «%2» supprimé</fr>
				<nl>Entry #%1 van de tabel &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; geschrapt</nl>
				<it>Entry # 1%di tabella &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; soppresso</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>fb17340dd900777d91d0f22940d712c4</id>
				<org>Fehler beim Löschen von #%1 aus Tabelle &quot;%2&quot;</org>
				<en>Error when deleting from table #%1 &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot;;</en>
				<es>Error al eliminar de la mesa #%1 &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot;</es>
				<fr>Erreur lors de la suppression de la table #%1 &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot;</fr>
				<nl>Fout bij het verwijderen van de tafel #%1 &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot;</nl>
				<it>Errore durante l&amp;#39;eliminazione dalla tabella #%1 &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot;</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>fd2e2099e065e78a7b7b34ef7b3b7cd0</id>
				<org>Bist du sicher, dass du diesen Eintrag löschen möchtest?</org>
				<en>Are you sure you want to delete this entry?</en>
				<es>¿Está seguro que quiere borrar esta entrada?</es>
				<fr>Etes-vous sûr de vouloir supprimer ce message?</fr>
				<nl>Weet u zeker dat u dit item wilt verwijderen?</nl>
				<it>Sei sicuro di voler cancellare questa voce?</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>50030925a405eb56bc19762688f93562</id>
				<org>Der Eintrag wurde erfolgreich gelöscht</org>
				<en>The entry was successfully deleted</en>
				<es>La entrada ha sido borrado</es>
				<fr>L&amp;#39;entrée a été supprimée</fr>
				<nl>De vermelding is succesvol verwijderd</nl>
				<it>La voce è stato cancellato con successo</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>94d7a3a7c488b016492e16d23ab96ee7</id>
				<org>Der Eintrag konnte nicht gelöscht werden</org>
				<en>The entry could not be deleted</en>
				<es>La entrada no debe ser borrada</es>
				<fr>L&amp;#39;entrée n&amp;#39;a pas pu être supprimé</fr>
				<nl>De inschrijving kan niet worden verwijderd</nl>
				<it>La voce non può essere cancellato</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>b586338b48ad922d12b9a008e108bb69</id>
				<org>Die folgenden Einträge konnte nicht gelöscht werden</org>
				<en>The following items could not be deleted</en>
				<es>Los siguientes artículos no podría suprimirse</es>
				<fr>Les éléments suivants n&amp;#39;ont pas pu être supprimé</fr>
				<nl>De volgende items kunnen niet worden verwijderd</nl>
				<it>I seguenti elementi non può essere cancellato</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>d1948655ca9b605f1df5de90c8276d18</id>
				<org>Die Einträge wurde erfolgreich gelöscht</org>
				<en>The entries were successfully deleted</en>
				<es>Las entradas se han eliminado correctamente</es>
				<fr>Les entrées ont été supprimées avec succès</fr>
				<nl>De inzendingen werden succesvol verwijderd</nl>
				<it>Le voci sono state eliminate correttamente</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>6592eed180ceb7b2eeef043779e68003</id>
				<org>Es wurden keine Einträge selektiert</org>
				<en>There were no entries selected</en>
				<es>No hubo entradas son seleccionados</es>
				<fr>Il n&amp;#39;y avait pas les entrées sont sélectionnées</fr>
				<nl>Er waren geen inzendingen zijn geselecteerd</nl>
				<it>Non ci sono state le voci vengono selezionati</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>4e04eb8e20dd8f7ec9cbbf0ad2b185fb</id>
				<org>Aktuelle Datei beibehalten</org>
				<en>Keep current file</en>
				<es>Archivo actual de mantenimiento</es>
				<fr>Fichier en cours maintenu</fr>
				<nl>Huidige bestand gehandhaafd</nl>
				<it>File corrente gestito</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>fc0ca0f38f5ae5091e705b46e2589430</id>
				<org>Bitte gib eine Email ein</org>
				<en>Please enter an email</en>
				<es>Por favor, escriba un e-mail</es>
				<fr>Entrez s&amp;#39;il vous plaît un e-mail</fr>
				<nl>Vul een e-mail</nl>
				<it>Si prega di inserire una e-mail</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>16f025dd551f373b0b7624cd11bce09c</id>
				<org>Die Adresse muss genau ein @-Zeichen enthalten</org>
				<en>The address must contain exactly one @ sign</en>
				<es>La dirección debe contener exactamente un signo &amp;quot;@&amp;quot;</es>
				<fr>L&amp;#39;adresse doit contenir exactement un signe @</fr>
				<nl>Het adres moet bevatten precies een @-teken</nl>
				<it>L&amp;#39;indirizzo deve contenere esattamente un segno @</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c8f279b9ef302d795004455a87ea0093</id>
				<org>Your name is %1 and your Email is %2</org>
				<en>Your name is %1 and your e-mail is %2</en>
				<es>Su nombre es%1 y tu e-mail es%2</es>
				<fr>Votre nom est%1 et votre e-mail est%2</fr>
				<nl>Uw naam is%1 en uw e-mail is%2</nl>
				<it>Il tuo nome è 1%e il tuo indirizzo e-mail è del 2%</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e46678cfa410e25e4d3e2398ac866c7d</id>
				<org>Bitte gib deine E-Mail-Adresse oder deine Lansuite-ID ein.</org>
				<en>Please enter your email address or your Lansuite ID.</en>
				<es>Por favor, introduzca su dirección de correo electrónico o su Lansuite ID.</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît, entrez votre adresse e-mail ou votre Lansuite ID.</fr>
				<nl>Vul uw e-mailadres of uw Lansuite ID.</nl>
				<it>Inserisci il tuo indirizzo e-mail o il tuo Lansuite ID.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c86f920d4c0db848c4fbe280d6f150db</id>
				<org>Bitte gib dein Kennwort ein.</org>
				<en>Please enter your password.</en>
				<es>Por favor, introduzca su contraseña.</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît entrer votre mot de passe.</fr>
				<nl>Geef uw wachtwoord in.</nl>
				<it>Inserisci la tua password.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>fdacaf37a0b8798dde0742571cc22fc6</id>
				<org>Dein Account ist gesperrt. Melde dich bitte bei der Organisation.</org>
				<en>Your account is locked. Get in touch with the organization.</en>
				<es>Su cuenta está bloqueada. Inicia sesión con la organización.</es>
				<fr>Votre compte est verrouillé. Connectez-vous avec l&amp;#39;organisation.</fr>
				<nl>Uw account is geblokkeerd. Log in met de organisatie.</nl>
				<it>Il tuo account è bloccato. Log in con l&amp;#39;organizzazione.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>4c9957b42093cea3b99c7838eb7a396c</id>
				<org>Dieser Account ist noch nicht freigeschaltet. Bitte warte ein Organisator dich freigeschaltet hat.</org>
				<en>This account is not activated yet. Please wait until an organizer, has unlocked you.</en>
				<es>Esta cuenta no está activada todavía. Por favor, espere hasta que un organizador, que la hayas desbloqueado.</es>
				<fr>Ce compte n&amp;#39;est pas encore activée. S&amp;#39;il vous plaît attendre jusqu&amp;#39;à ce qu&amp;#39;un organisateur, vous avez déverrouillé.</fr>
				<nl>Deze account is nog niet geactiveerd. Gelieve even te wachten tot er een organisator, heb je ontgrendeld.</nl>
				<it>Questo account non è ancora attivato. Si prega di attendere fino a quando un organizzatore, si è sbloccato.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>3fd404486b4f50f32046ff95bbb7c1c8</id>
				<org>Solltest du dein Passwort vergessen haben, wende dich bitte an die Organisation.</org>
				<en>If you have forgotten your password, please contact the organization.</en>
				<es>Si has olvidado tu contraseña, por favor, póngase en contacto con la organización.</es>
				<fr>Si vous avez oublié votre mot de passe, s&amp;#39;il vous plaît contacter l&amp;#39;organisation.</fr>
				<nl>Als u uw wachtwoord vergeten bent, neem dan contact op met de organisatie.</nl>
				<it>Se hai dimenticato la password, si prega di contattare l&amp;#39;organizzazione.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>8713ef28cc370203b5992ded034f23c9</id>
				<org>Wenn ihr Broswer keine IFrames unterstützt,</org>
				<en>If your Broswer does not support IFrames,</en>
				<es>Si su navegador no soporta iframes,</es>
				<fr>Si Votre navigateur ne supporte pas les iframes,</fr>
				<nl>Als uw Browser ondersteunt geen iframes,</nl>
				<it>Se il tuo Broswer non supporta IFrames,</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>926c6aaecc36c5f8fde83bc353aa0297</id>
				<org>bitte hier klicken!</org>
				<en>click here!</en>
				<es>haga clic aquí!</es>
				<fr>cliquez ici!</fr>
				<nl>Klik hier!</nl>
				<it>clicca qui!</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>fd04b192ef33d3ad06d3659556f398e1</id>
				<org>Unable to Initialize new GD image stream</org>
				<en>Unable to Initialize new GD image stream</en>
				<es>No se puede inicializar flujo GD nueva imagen</es>
				<fr>Impossible d&amp;#39;initialiser les flux de nouvelle image GD</fr>
				<nl>Kan nieuwe GD image stream Initialize</nl>
				<it>In grado di inizializzare flusso GD nuova immagine</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>bdc6bb23f90ba20f579c05a83f11fc60</id>
				<org>Diese ID existiert nicht.</org>
				<en>This ID does not exist.</en>
				<es>Este identificador no existe.</es>
				<fr>Cette pièce d&amp;#39;identité n&amp;#39;existe pas.</fr>
				<nl>Deze ID bestaat niet.</nl>
				<it>Questo ID non esiste.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e7667b33a716b582c1b1ba453c5b82ad</id>
				<org>Bitte fülle dieses Pflichtfeld aus.</org>
				<en>Please fill out this required field.</en>
				<es>Por favor, rellene el campo requerido.</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît remplir ce champ obligatoire.</fr>
				<nl>Vul dit verplicht veld.</nl>
				<it>Si prega di compilare questo campo obbligatorio.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>46985c8e1b7a587fa61d38da8204e0e8</id>
				<org>Bitte gib eine Zahl ein.</org>
				<en>Please enter a number.</en>
				<es>Por favor, introduzca un número.</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît, entrez un numéro.</fr>
				<nl>Voer een getal.</nl>
				<it>Si prega di inserire un numero.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>f2735adcfb12c192808f0f7d540b84de</id>
				<org>Das eingegebene Datum ist nicht korrekt.</org>
				<en>The date entered is not correct.</en>
				<es>La fecha de entrada no es correcta.</es>
				<fr>La date d&amp;#39;entrée n&amp;#39;est pas correct.</fr>
				<nl>De datum ingevoerd is niet correct.</nl>
				<it>La data di entrata non è corretto.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>be98325d4cd729f722f203e4ef8e4e05</id>
				<org>Die beiden Kennworte stimmen nicht überein.</org>
				<en>The two passwords do not match.</en>
				<es>Las dos contraseñas no coinciden.</es>
				<fr>Les deux mots de passe ne correspondent pas.</fr>
				<nl>De twee wachtwoorden komen niet overeen.</nl>
				<it>Le due password non corrispondono.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>a106ae47f0685b677e005c6b66f70fed</id>
				<org>Captcha falsch wiedergegeben.</org>
				<en>Captcha misrepresented.</en>
				<es>Captcha tergiversado.</es>
				<fr>Captcha dénaturés.</fr>
				<nl>Captcha verkeerd.</nl>
				<it>Captcha travisata.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>091963481969407cc37f9db9d5461aaf</id>
				<org>Dieser Eintrag existiert bereits in unserer Datenbank.</org>
				<en>This entry already exists in our database.</en>
				<es>Esta entrada ya existe en nuestra base de datos.</es>
				<fr>Cette entrée existe déjà dans notre base de données.</fr>
				<nl>Dit item bestaat al in onze database.</nl>
				<it>Questa voce esiste già nel nostro database.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>3f0a8c5abec0b8ae2d072736c64aa0fe</id>
				<org>Verfikation</org>
				<en>Verfikation</en>
				<es>Verfikation</es>
				<fr>Verfikation</fr>
				<nl>Verfikation</nl>
				<it>Verfikation</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5d6c931b136c70de3a474e3b5a8c16b8</id>
				<org>Die Daten wurden erfolgreich geändert.</org>
				<en>The data has been successfully changed.</en>
				<es>Los datos se han cambiado correctamente.</es>
				<fr>Les données ont été changé avec succès.</fr>
				<nl>De data is met succes veranderd.</nl>
				<it>I dati sono stati modificati.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>8e2bad1e73058893df1b6b23093898fb</id>
				<org>Die Daten wurden erfolgreich eingefügt.</org>
				<en>The data were successfully inserted.</en>
				<es>Los datos han sido correctamente insertada.</es>
				<fr>Les données ont été correctement insérés.</fr>
				<nl>De gegevens werden succesvol geplaatst.</nl>
				<it>I dati sono stati correttamente inseriti.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>92786d2b05eb02d0bb9a427cc33d52b5</id>
				<org>Function setainfo needs Priority defined as Integer: 0 low (grey), 1 middle (green), 2 high (orange)</org>
				<en>Function setainfo needs priority defined as Integer: 0 low (gray), 1 middle (green), 2 high (orange)</en>
				<es>Prioridad setainfo Función necesidades definidas como INTEGER: 0 bajas (gris), 1 medio (verde), 2 de alto (naranja)</es>
				<fr>Fonction des besoins prioritaires setainfo définie comme INTEGER: 0 faible (gris), 1 milieu (vert), 2 haut (orange)</fr>
				<nl>Functie setainfo prioritaire behoeften gedefinieerd als Integer: 0 laag (grijs), 1 midden (groen), 2 hoog (oranje)</nl>
				<it>Priorità setainfo Funzione esigenze definite come Integer: 0 basso (grigio), 1 media (verde), 2 High (arancione)</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>35cb2d80a11eadd1c880fc69cb852f76</id>
				<org>Sonntag</org>
				<en>Sunday</en>
				<es>Domingo</es>
				<fr>Dimanche</fr>
				<nl>Zondag</nl>
				<it>Domenica</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5ba92fd9fe06536b98e6ab7b19531d8f</id>
				<org>Montag</org>
				<en>Monday</en>
				<es>Lunes</es>
				<fr>Lundi</fr>
				<nl>Maandag</nl>
				<it>Lunedi</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>af5b4a59f444f0b452421dcf5238f781</id>
				<org>Dienstag</org>
				<en>Tuesday</en>
				<es>Martes</es>
				<fr>Mardi</fr>
				<nl>Dinsdag</nl>
				<it>Martedì</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c7ce86340399fcbc38c020a090e5f227</id>
				<org>Mittwoch</org>
				<en>Wednesday</en>
				<es>Miércoles</es>
				<fr>Mercredi</fr>
				<nl>Woensdag</nl>
				<it>Mercoledì</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c4c15efd19d7e642741a346807510abe</id>
				<org>Donnerstag</org>
				<en>Thursday</en>
				<es>Jueves</es>
				<fr>Jeudi</fr>
				<nl>Donderdag</nl>
				<it>Giovedi</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>8e968f5fc3fddc3f1c7d9510b22b4ada</id>
				<org>Freitag</org>
				<en>Friday</en>
				<es>Viernes</es>
				<fr>Vendredi</fr>
				<nl>Vrijdag</nl>
				<it>Venerdì</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>f3e9b5cbb5bfb05906a402de29d7ee6f</id>
				<org>Samstag</org>
				<en>Saturday</en>
				<es>Sábado</es>
				<fr>Samedi</fr>
				<nl>Zaterdag</nl>
				<it>Sabato</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e2e0ab9c9510bf61fd17296bae8d3d24</id>
				<org>So</org>
				<en>Sun</en>
				<es>Tan</es>
				<fr>Ainsi</fr>
				<nl>Zo</nl>
				<it>Così</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c08df9bb5fb44242a6291b1eee5d09ad</id>
				<org>Mo</org>
				<en>Mon</en>
				<es>Lun.</es>
				<fr>Lun.</fr>
				<nl>Maan</nl>
				<it>Mon</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>5961102bbf53b3ac0b9085f1ef3ce3f0</id>
				<org>Di</org>
				<en>Tue</en>
				<es>Mar</es>
				<fr>Mar.</fr>
				<nl>Dins</nl>
				<it>Mar</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>0567953871b1bf589b797d9b178d5a94</id>
				<org>Do</org>
				<en>Thu</en>
				<es>Jue</es>
				<fr>Jeu.</fr>
				<nl>Don</nl>
				<it>Gio</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>fa717ba17306cd76900510df8ac8013e</id>
				<org>Fr</org>
				<en>Fri</en>
				<es>Vie</es>
				<fr>Ven.</fr>
				<nl>Vrij</nl>
				<it>Ven</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e55bb1ae59b6a64858a85a2f48c53036</id>
				<org>Sa</org>
				<en>Sat</en>
				<es>Sáb</es>
				<fr>Sam.</fr>
				<nl>Zat</nl>
				<it>Sab</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>008d04f41ae4d1009111a68de817d0f4</id>
				<org>Du hast keine Zugriffsrechte für diesen Bereich.</org>
				<en>You do not have access to that area.</en>
				<es>Usted no tiene acceso a esa zona.</es>
				<fr>Vous n&amp;#39;avez pas accès à cette zone.</fr>
				<nl>U heeft geen toegang tot dat gebied.</nl>
				<it>Non si dispone di accesso a quella zona.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e7ba52be00619245bf487b34e862db3c</id>
				<org>Du bist nicht eingeloggt. Bitte logge dich erst ein, bevor du diesen Bereich betrittst.</org>
				<en>You are not logged. Please log in first before you enter this area.</en>
				<es>No está conectado. Debes iniciar sesión antes de entrar en esta área.</es>
				<fr>Vous n&amp;#39;êtes pas connecté. S&amp;#39;il vous plaît Connectez-vous en premier avant de pénétrer dans cette zone.</fr>
				<nl>U bent niet ingelogd. Gelieve eerst in te loggen voordat u dit gebied.</nl>
				<it>Lei non è registrato. Vi preghiamo di entrare in prima prima di entrare in questo settore.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>b88306302f2681ea25c7ea17d545a037</id>
				<org>Leider ist die von dir aufgerufene Seite auf diesem Server nicht vorhanden.&lt;br/&gt;Um Fehler zu vermeiden, solltest du die URL nicht manuell ändern, sondern die Links benutzen. Wenn du die Adresse manuell eingegeben hast überprüfe bitte die URL.</org>
				<en>Unfortunately, the page you requested does not exist on this server. &lt;br/&gt; To avoid errors, you should not change the URL manually, but use the links. If you have manually entered the address, please check the URL.</en>
				<es>Lamentablemente, la página solicitada no existe en este servidor. &lt;br/&gt; Para evitar errores, no se debe cambiar la dirección manualmente, pero el uso de los enlaces. Si ha introducido manualmente la dirección, por favor, compruebe el URL.</es>
				<fr>Malheureusement, la page demandée n&amp;#39;existe pas sur ce serveur. &lt;br/&gt; Pour éviter les erreurs, vous ne devez pas modifier l&amp;#39;URL manuellement, mais utilisez les liens. Si vous avez saisi manuellement l&amp;#39;adresse, s&amp;#39;il vous plaît vérifier l</fr>
				<nl>Helaas, de pagina die u heeft opgevraagd bestaat niet op deze server. &lt;br/&gt; Om fouten te vermijden, moet je niet veranderen de URL handmatig, maar gebruik de links. Als u handmatig hebt ingevoerd het adres, kijk dan op de URL.</nl>
				<it>Purtroppo, la pagina che hai richiesto non esiste su questo server. &lt;br/&gt; Per evitare errori, non si dovrebbe modificare l&amp;#39;URL manualmente, ma utilizzare i collegamenti. Se hai inserito manualmente l&amp;#39;indirizzo, si prega di consultare l&amp;#39;URL.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>93bfd0b61624a3812335be027c2134c6</id>
				<org>Dieses Lansuite Modul wurde deaktiviert und steht somit nicht zur Verfügung.</org>
				<en>This Lansuite module was disabled and is therefore not available.</en>
				<es>Este módulo Lansuite se ha desactivado y por lo tanto no está disponible.</es>
				<fr>Ce module Lansuite a été désactivé et donc pas disponibles.</fr>
				<nl>Deze Lansuite module is uitgeschakeld en dus niet beschikbaar.</nl>
				<it>Questo modulo Lansuite è stato disattivato e quindi non disponibile.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>4f712108e0e13abdfd131cfa68799338</id>
				<org>Du hast diese Anfrage wiederholt ausgeführt.</org>
				<en>They have repeatedly stated this request.</en>
				<es>Ellos han declarado en repetidas ocasiones esta petición.</es>
				<fr>Ils ont déclaré à plusieurs reprises cette demande.</fr>
				<nl>Zij hebben herhaaldelijk verklaard dit verzoek.</nl>
				<it>Hanno ripetutamente dichiarato che questa richiesta.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>ee65867e7d6715ac23dcea8252c8e0e8</id>
				<org>Falsche Email angegeben (%1)</org>
				<en>Incorrect email specified (%1)</en>
				<es>Correo electrónico incorrecta especificado (%1)</es>
				<fr>E-mail incorrecte spécifiée (%1)</fr>
				<nl>Onjuist e-mail specified (%1)</nl>
				<it>E-mail non corretto specificato (1%)</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>baea7a0b9f07f1840ebe1a51f13cb692</id>
				<org>Login für %1 fehlgeschlagen (Account gesperrt).</org>
				<en>Login for %1 failed (blocked account).</en>
				<es>Inicio de sesión para%1 no (bloqueado la cuenta).</es>
				<fr>Connectez-vous pour%1 a échoué (compte bloqué).</fr>
				<nl>Login voor%1 is mislukt (geblokkeerde rekening).</nl>
				<it>Login per%1 non riuscita (bloccato il conto).</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>abbd6872535b63a36b7e86d6f01d4a75</id>
				<org>Account von %1 ist noch gesperrt. Login daher fehlgeschlagen.</org>
				<en>Account of %1 is still locked. Login therefore failed.</en>
				<es>Cuenta de 1%sigue bloqueada. Ingresar por lo tanto no.</es>
				<fr>Compte de%1 est toujours verrouillé. Connectez-vous donc échoué.</fr>
				<nl>Rekening van%1 is nog steeds geblokkeerd. Log dus mislukt.</nl>
				<it>Conto di%1 è ancora bloccata. Login quindi venuta meno.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>ee4afd2e88681d11061cfd86d628a180</id>
				<org>Login für %1 fehlgeschlagen (Passwort-Fehler).</org>
				<en>Login failed for %1 (password error).</en>
				<es>Error de acceso para%1) (Error de la contraseña.</es>
				<fr>Échec de la connexion%1) (erreur de mot de passe.</fr>
				<nl>Aanmelding mislukt voor%1) (wachtwoord fout.</nl>
				<it>Accesso non riuscito per l&amp;#39;1%) (errore di password.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>d9bfb5a529828b84f45ae74c90eafd9a</id>
				<org>Login für %1 fehlgeschlagen (Account nicht eingecheckt).</org>
				<en>Login for %1 failed (account not checked in).</en>
				<es>Inicio de sesión para%1 no (no cuenta activada).</es>
				<fr>Connectez-vous pour%1 a échoué (compte non vérifié).</fr>
				<nl>Login voor%1 is mislukt (rekening niet aangevinkt).</nl>
				<it>Login per%1 fallito (non conto controllato).</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>4b91da1b817b09176d25cb1dfad65c59</id>
				<org>Login für %1 fehlgeschlagen (Account ausgecheckt).</org>
				<en>Login for %1 failed (account checked out).</en>
				<es>Inicio de sesión para%1 no (cuenta desprotegido).</es>
				<fr>Connectez-vous pour%1 a échoué (compte vérifié).</fr>
				<nl>Login voor%1 is mislukt (rekening gecontroleerd).</nl>
				<it>Login per%1 non riuscita (estratto conto).</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e57ab199a2074f450c154dfd84296615</id>
				<org>Unable to write in directory /'/%1/'/</org>
				<en>Unable to write to directory %1</en>
				<es>%No se puede escribir en el directorio / &amp;#39;/ 1 /&amp;#39; /</es>
				<fr>Impossible d&amp;#39;écrire dans le répertoire / &amp;#39;/%1 /&amp;#39; /</fr>
				<nl>Kan niet schrijven naar de directory / &amp;#39;/%1 /&amp;#39; /</nl>
				<it>In grado di scrivere nella directory / &amp;#39;/%1 /&amp;#39; /</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>93b264adaeca55feeb7ec542bda031fe</id>
				<org>Eintrag #%1 in Tabelle &quot;%2&quot; geändert</org>
				<en>Changed entry #%1 of table &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot;</en>
				<es>Entrada #%1 de la tabla &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; última</es>
				<fr>Entrée #%1 du tableau «%2» Dernière</fr>
				<nl>Entry #%1 van de tabel &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; laatste</nl>
				<it>Entry # 1%di tabella &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; ultimo</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>1fdad29030e08f56ede1f2bd22bc2d68</id>
				<org>Eintrag #%1 in Tabelle &quot;%2&quot; eingefügt</org>
				<en>Entry #%1 of table &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; was inserted</en>
				<es>Entrada #%1 de la tabla &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; se insertan</es>
				<fr>Entrée #%1 du tableau «%2» est inséré</fr>
				<nl>Entry #%1 van de tabel &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; ingevoegd</nl>
				<it>Entry # 1%di tabella &amp;quot;%2&amp;quot; è inserito</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e78eb734f37b3a978031b4871805d3a0</id>
				<org>Diese Email ist ungültig (Falscher Benutzer-Teil)</org>
				<en>This email is invalid (incorrect user part)</en>
				<es>Este correo electrónico no es válida (parte de usuario incorrecto)</es>
				<fr>Ce courriel n&amp;#39;est pas valide (partie utilisateur incorrect)</fr>
				<nl>Deze e-mail is ongeldig (onjuist gebruiker deel)</nl>
				<it>Questa email non è valido (parte dell&amp;#39;utente non corretto)</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>a01b15fee683b2dc8fda9114c9c3c7c7</id>
				<org>Diese Email ist ungültig (Falscher Host-Teil)</org>
				<en>This email is invalid (Wrong host part)</en>
				<es>Este correo electrónico no es válida (parte de host incorrecto)</es>
				<fr>Cet e-mail est invalide (partie hôte Wrong)</fr>
				<nl>Deze e-mail is ongeldig (Wrong host-deel)</nl>
				<it>Questa email non è valido (parte host Wrong)</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>21b62c8fbb71b3fb65bb42e0648c4ae4</id>
				<org>Diese Email ist ungültig (Nicht exitsierende Domain)</org>
				<en>This email is invalid (Non existing domain)</en>
				<es>Este correo electrónico no es válida de dominio (no exitsierende)</es>
				<fr>Ce courriel est invalide domaine (et non exitsierende)</fr>
				<nl>Deze e-mail is ongeldig (Niet exitsierende Domain)</nl>
				<it>Questa email non è valido (non exitsierende Domain)</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>fee3153d8768a82e13b08e0aff29a0a9</id>
				<org>AddTableRow: First argument needs to be array</org>
				<en>AddTableRow: First argument needs to be array</en>
				<es>AddTableRow: Primer argumento debe ser amplia</es>
				<fr>AddTableRow: Le premier argument doit être array</fr>
				<nl>AddTableRow: Eerste argument moet worden array</nl>
				<it>AddTableRow: primo argomento deve essere di matrice</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>9cfe2c498f503819331e809d47fd5145</id>
				<org>AddTableRow: First argument needs to be 2-dimension-array</org>
				<en>AddTableRow: First argument needs to be 2-dimensional array</en>
				<es>AddTableRow: Primer argumento debe ser 2-matriz bidimensional</es>
				<fr>AddTableRow: Le premier argument doit être tableau à 2 dimensions</fr>
				<nl>AddTableRow: Eerste argument moet worden 2-dimensionale array</nl>
				<it>AddTableRow: primo argomento deve essere 2-array monodimensionale</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>9baed4461ee81660fff41f6f70389834</id>
				<org>Das MySQL-PHP Modul ist nicht geladen. Bitte füge die mysql.so Erweiterung zur php.ini hinzu und restarte den Webserver neu. Lansuite wird abgebrochen</org>
				<en>The MySQL PHP module is not loaded. Please add the mysql.so extension to php.ini and restart the web server. Lansuite is canceled</en>
				<es>El módulo de PHP de MySQL no está cargado. Por favor, añada la extensión mysql.so a php.ini y reinicie el servidor web. Lansuite se cancela</es>
				<fr>Le module PHP pour MySQL n&amp;#39;est pas chargé. S&amp;#39;il vous plaît ajoutez l&amp;#39;extension mysql.so à votre php.ini et redémarrez le serveur web. Lansuite est annulée</fr>
				<nl>De MySQL PHP-module is niet geladen. Voeg de mysql.so uitbreiding tot php.ini en start de webserver. Lansuite geannuleerd</nl>
				<it>Il modulo MySQL PHP non è caricato. Si prega di aggiungere l&amp;#39;estensione mysql.so di php.ini e riavviare il server web. Lansuite viene annullata</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>7dbe4e409654309e8dc548ef8224b1c4</id>
				<org>SQL-Failure. Database respondet: &lt;b&gt;%1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Query: &lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;%2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Script: &lt;a href=&quot;%3&quot;&gt;%3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Referrer: &lt;a href=&quot;%4&quot;&gt;%4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</org>
				<en>SQL-Failure. Respondet &lt;b&gt;Database:%1&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Query: &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;%2&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%3&quot;&gt;Script:%3&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%4&quot;&gt;Referrer:%4&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;</en>
				<es>SQL-No. Respondet &lt;b&gt;base de datos:%1&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Consulta: &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;%2&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%3&quot;&gt;Guión:%3&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%4&quot;&gt;Referente:%4&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;</es>
				<fr>SQL-échec. Respondet &lt;b&gt;Base de données:%1&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Requête: &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;%2&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%3&quot;&gt;Scénario:%3&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%4&quot;&gt;Référence:%4&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;</fr>
				<nl>SQL-Failure. Respondet &lt;b&gt;Database:%1&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Zoeken: &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;%2&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%3&quot;&gt;Script:%3&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%4&quot;&gt;Referrer:%4&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;</nl>
				<it>SQL-Failure. Respondet &lt;b&gt;Database:%1&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Query: &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;2%&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%3&quot;&gt;Script:%3&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;%4&quot;&gt;Referente:%4&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt;</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>b5632fc6b89802e9371a3306a3cf2dd3</id>
				<org>Die Verbindung zur Datenbank ist fehlgeschlagen. Lansuite wird abgebrochen</org>
				<en>The connection to the database failed. Lansuite is canceled</en>
				<es>La conexión a la base de datos ha fallado. Lansuite se cancela</es>
				<fr>La connexion à la base de données a échoué. Lansuite est annulée</fr>
				<nl>De verbinding met de database mislukt. Lansuite geannuleerd</nl>
				<it>La connessione al database non riuscita. Lansuite viene annullata</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>d0c08536fefba309d182e260da4c2f8b</id>
				<org>Die Datenbank '%1' konnte nicht ausgewählt werden. Lansuite wird abgebrochen</org>
				<en>The database '%1' could not be selected. Lansuite is canceled</en>
				<es>La base de datos%&amp;#39;1&amp;#39; no podía ser seleccionado. Lansuite se cancela</es>
				<fr>%La base de données &amp;#39;1&amp;#39; n&amp;#39;a pas pu être sélectionné. Lansuite est annulée</fr>
				<nl>De database%&amp;quot;1&amp;quot; kon niet worden geselecteerd. Lansuite geannuleerd</nl>
				<it>Il database%&amp;#39;1&amp;#39; non potevano essere selezionati. Lansuite viene annullata</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>55bd68d08421681ecb999d9edf5c577f</id>
				<org>Dieser Eintrag kann momentan leider nicht gelöscht werden, da Einträge aus folgender Tabelle noch darauf referenzieren</org>
				<en>This entry can not be deleted at the moment, for referenced in the following tables exists</en>
				<es>Esta entrada se puede eliminar por el momento no, como se indica en las entradas de la siguiente tabla se sigue sin</es>
				<fr>Cette inscription ne peut être supprimé pour l&amp;#39;instant n&amp;#39;a pas, comme référencé dans le tableau ci-dessous les entrées toujours pas</fr>
				<nl>Dit item kan worden geschrapt op het moment niet, zoals genoemd in de volgende tabel vermeldingen nog steeds buiten</nl>
				<it>Questa iscrizione può essere eliminato al momento non è, come indicato nei seguenti voci tabella ancora fuori</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c78ad4525df77d469a93e3b99fba4c8d</id>
				<org>Dieser Eintrag kann momentan leider nicht gelöscht werden, da Einträge aus folgenden Tabellen noch darauf referenzieren</org>
				<en>This entry can not be deleted at the moment, for referenced in the following tables exists</en>
				<es>Esta entrada se puede eliminar en el momento, lamentablemente no, como mensajes de referencia a los siguientes cuadros todavía fuera</es>
				<fr>Cette inscription ne peut être supprimé à l&amp;#39;instant, malheureusement, pas en tant que messages référençant les tableaux qui suivent toujours pas</fr>
				<nl>Dit item kan worden geschrapt op het moment, helaas, niet als berichten referencement de volgende tabellen nog steeds uit</nl>
				<it>Questa iscrizione può essere cancellata al momento, purtroppo, non, come messaggi fa riferimento alle seguenti tabelle ancora fuori</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>be0d3bb5a0f52755701fafef5c2391e0</id>
				<org>Achtung</org>
				<en>Attention</en>
				<es>Considerar</es>
				<fr>Observer</fr>
				<nl>Hoogachting</nl>
				<it>Considerazione</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>06552ef259e791e5e88dc6a347651518</id>
				<org>Folgende Einträge referenzieren noch auf diesen Eintrag:</org>
				<en>The following entries still refer to this entry:</en>
				<es>Las siguientes entradas se refieren todavía a esta entrada:</es>
				<fr>Les entrées suivantes se réfèrent toujours à cette note:</fr>
				<nl>De volgende vermeldingen nog steeds te verwijzen naar dit item:</nl>
				<it>Le seguenti voci si riferiscono ancora a questo articolo:</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>abec5598c9fed0b86e761e5b3e9ae25c</id>
				<org>Diese Eintrag werden mitgelöscht!</org>
				<en>This entry will also be deleted!</en>
				<es>Esta entrada también será eliminado!</es>
				<fr>Cette inscription sera également supprimé!</fr>
				<nl>Dit item zal ook worden verwijderd!</nl>
				<it>Questa voce sarà cancellato!</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>27605f86aebd3703b7482f752d4a65ee</id>
				<org>Bei Einträge in dieser Tabelle wird die Zuordnung aufgelöst!</org>
				<en>For entries in this table, the association is dissolved!</en>
				<es>Para las entradas en esta mesa, que se disuelva la asociación!</es>
				<fr>Pour les entrées dans ce tableau, l&amp;#39;association est dissoute!</fr>
				<nl>Voor vermeldingen in deze tabel, is de vereniging ontbonden!</nl>
				<it>Per le voci in questa tabella, l&amp;#39;associazione è sciolta!</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>570a74121731becb928c0c6f00c7976b</id>
				<org>Vollbildmodus schließen</org>
				<en>Close Full Screen</en>
				<es>Cerrar pantalla completa</es>
				<fr>Fermer le plein écran</fr>
				<nl>Sluiten Full Screen</nl>
				<it>Chiudi schermo intero</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>4789ac07952deecf2a4ae4276ef5caad</id>
				<org>Seite</org>
				<en>Side</en>
				<es>Lado</es>
				<fr>Côté</fr>
				<nl>Zijkant</nl>
				<it>Lato</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>df24d29109c2ee42527311d45a2f3e19</id>
				<org>Diese Webseite ist Momentan im &quot;Freeze-Mode&quot;.[br]D.h. es können keine neuen Daten in die Datenbank geschrieben werden.[br][br]Bitte versuche es zu einem Späteren Zeitpunkt nocheinmal.</org>
				<en>This website is currently in &amp;quot;freeze mode&amp;quot;. [Br] That is, it is not possible to write any new data into the database. [Br] [br] Please try again at a later time.</en>
				<es>Este sitio web está actualmente en modo de la &amp;quot;congelación&amp;quot;. [Br] Esto es, es posible escribir nuevos datos en la base de datos. [Br] [br] Por favor, inténtelo de nuevo más tarde.</es>
				<fr>Ce site est actuellement en mode &amp;quot;geler&amp;quot;. [Fr] Cela est, il est possible d&amp;#39;écrire de nouvelles données dans la base de données. [Br] [br] S&amp;#39;il vous plaît essayer de nouveau à une date ultérieure.</fr>
				<nl>Deze website is momenteel in de &amp;quot;freeze mode&amp;quot;. [Br] Dat is, is het mogelijk om alle nieuwe gegevens in de database te schrijven. [Br] [br] Probeer het opnieuw op een later tijdstip.</nl>
				<it>Questo sito è attualmente in modalità di &amp;quot;congelare&amp;quot;. [Br] Questo è, è possibile scrivere i nuovi dati nel database. [Br] [br] Si prega di riprovare in un secondo momento.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>46b4090bea4fb9cef4c9982be7b208f7</id>
				<org>Dieses Feld enthält nicht erlaubte Steuerungszeichen (z.B. einen Tab, oder Zeilenumbruch)</org>
				<en>This field contains permitted control characters (such as a tab, or newline)</en>
				<es>Este campo no contiene caracteres de control autorizados (como una ficha, o salto de línea)</es>
				<fr>Ce champ ne contient pas permis de caractères de contrôle (comme un onglet, ou saut de ligne)</fr>
				<nl>Dit veld bevat geen toegestaan controle tekens (zoals een tab of newline)</nl>
				<it>Questo campo non contiene caratteri di controllo autorizzati (come ad esempio una scheda, o newline)</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>78ce20219f0f80bd2e6f5e991f4295ef</id>
				<org>Bitte gib diesen Text unterhalb ein</org>
				<en>Please enter the text below</en>
				<es>Por favor, introduzca el texto de la caída por debajo de un</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît entrez la chute en dessous d&amp;#39;un texte</fr>
				<nl>Gelieve de tekst invoeren vallen onder een</nl>
				<it>Inserisci il testo di sotto di una caduta</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>1a86641e4cd940fd2a55e2a4238b0e4b</id>
				<org>Die Mail-Domain %1 ist nicht erlaubt, da sie Anbieter von &quot;Wegwerf-Mails&quot; ist</org>
				<en>The mail domain %1 is not allowed because they are offering &amp;quot;disposable emails&amp;quot;</en>
				<es>El 1%dominio de correo electrónico no está permitido, ya que ofrece un correo &amp;quot;desechable&amp;quot;, es</es>
				<fr>Le domaine de messagerie%1 n&amp;#39;est pas autorisé, car ils offrent «courriels jetables» est</fr>
				<nl>De mail domein%1 is niet toegestaan omdat ze aanbieden &amp;quot;wegwerp e-mails&amp;quot; is</nl>
				<it>Il dominio di posta%1 non è consentito, perché offerta &amp;quot;e-mail usa e getta&amp;quot; è</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>e6b431736c96f4307e84d3fe19f1b14f</id>
				<org>Du hast deine Email-Adresse (%1) noch nicht verifiziert. Bitte folge dem Link in der dir zugestellten Email.</org>
				<en>You have not yet verified your email address (%1). Please follow the link in the e-mail delivered to you.</en>
				<es>Todavía no ha verificado su dirección de correo electrónico (%1). Por favor siga el enlace en el e-mail que le ofrece.</es>
				<fr>Vous n&amp;#39;avez pas encore validé votre adresse e-mail (%1). S&amp;#39;il vous plaît suivez le lien dans l&amp;#39;e-mail vous est livré.</fr>
				<nl>U heeft nog niet gecontroleerd uw e-mailadres (%1). Volg de link in de e-mail bij u geleverd.</nl>
				<it>Non hai ancora verificato il tuo indirizzo e-mail (1%). Segui il link nella e-mail consegnato a voi.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>f2999f6023f7896c13d6f3ca77985cb9</id>
				<org>Klicke hier, um die Mail erneut zu versenden&lt;/a&gt;</org>
				<en>Click here to resend the mail to</en>
				<es>Haga clic aquí para reenviar el correo a</es>
				<fr>Cliquez ici pour renvoyer le courrier à</fr>
				<nl>Klik hier om opnieuw te verzenden van de mail naar</nl>
				<it>Clicca qui per inviare nuovamente la posta a</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>116157fc9c4516dd2e35512965048960</id>
				<org>Hast du dein Passwort vergessen?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/index.php?mod=usrmgr&amp;action=pwrecover&quot;/&gt;Hier kannst du dir ein neues Passwort generieren&lt;/a&gt;.</org>
				<en>Forgot your password? &amp;lt;br/&amp;gt; &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;/index.php?mod=usrmgr&amp;amp;action=pwrecover&amp;quot;/&amp;gt;Here you can generate a new password.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;</en>
				<es>¿Olvidaste tu contraseña? &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/index.php?mod=usrmgr&amp;action=pwrecover&quot;/&gt;Aquí se puede generar una contraseña nueva.&lt;/a&gt;</es>
				<fr>Vous avez oublié votre mot de passe? &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/index.php?mod=usrmgr&amp;action=pwrecover&quot;/&gt;Ici vous pouvez générer un mot de passe nouveau.&lt;/a&gt;</fr>
				<nl>Wachtwoord vergeten? &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/index.php?mod=usrmgr&amp;action=pwrecover&quot;/&gt;Hier kunt u het genereren van een nieuw wachtwoord.&lt;/a&gt;</nl>
				<it>Hai dimenticato la password? &lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;/index.php?mod=usrmgr&amp;action=pwrecover&quot;/&gt;Qui è possibile generare una password nuova.&lt;/a&gt;</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>811e47f41d8090c0c509dea9cefcebab</id>
				<org>Deine Session ist abgelaufen und das bei dir gesetzte Cookie ist fehlerhaft. Leider konntest du damit nicht eingeloggt werden. Bitte logge dich erneut manuell ein</org>
				<en>Your session has expired and the cookie set is corrupt. Unfortunately, you were unable to be logged in. Please log in manually again</en>
				<es>Su sesión ha caducado y se establece la &amp;quot;cookie&amp;quot; es corrupto. Desafortunadamente, usted no pudo estar conectado. Inicia sesión, además de manualmente</es>
				<fr>Votre session a expiré et que vous définissez le cookie est endommagé. Malheureusement, vous n&amp;#39;avez pas pu être identifié. S&amp;#39;il vous plaît Connectez-vous en plus manuellement</fr>
				<nl>Je sessie is verlopen en u de cookie is beschadigd. Helaas, je was niet in staat te zijn ingelogd. Log in aanvulling op handmatig</nl>
				<it>La sessione è scaduta e si imposta il cookie è danneggiato. Purtroppo, sono stati in grado di essere registrato. Accedi oltre al manuale</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>efb0658c8f86ed490e10279b55332adc</id>
				<org>Login für %1 fehlgeschlagen (Cookie-Fehler).</org>
				<en>Login failed for %1 (Cookie error).</en>
				<es>Error de acceso para%1) (Error de cookies.</es>
				<fr>Échec de la connexion%1) (Erreur de cookie.</fr>
				<nl>Aanmelding mislukt voor%1) (Cookie fout.</nl>
				<it>Accesso non riuscito per l&amp;#39;1%) (Errore del cookie.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>77247842e26d2464303c900fb85ac152</id>
				<org>Benutzerwechsel erfolgreich. Die &amp;Auml;nderungen werden beim laden der nächsten Seite wirksam.</org>
				<en>Users change successful. The changes will take effect when the next page loads.</en>
				<es>Usuarios de cambio con éxito. Los cambios surtirán efecto cuando la página siguiente a la carga.</es>
				<fr>Utilisateurs changement réussi. Les modifications prendront effet dès la prochaine page à charger.</fr>
				<nl>Gebruikers verandering succesvol. De wijzigingen worden van kracht wanneer de volgende pagina te laden.</nl>
				<it>Agli utenti di modificare successo. Le modifiche entreranno in vigore quando la pagina successiva per caricare.</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>f0be8e71454169b8beabad79e1437fd3</id>
				<org>Fehlerhafte Cookie-Daten. Cookie wurde gelöscht</org>
				<en>Incorrect cookie data. Cookie has been deleted</en>
				<es>Datos de la cookie incorrecto. Cookie se ha suprimido</es>
				<fr>Données du cookie incorrect. Cookie a été supprimé</fr>
				<nl>Onjuiste cookie-gegevens. Cookie is geschrapt</nl>
				<it>Dati del cookie non corretto. Cookie è stato eliminato</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>ce1e61624f032f37a338b7eccc05a90c</id>
				<org>Mi</org>
				<en>Wed</en>
				<es>Mié</es>
				<fr>Mer</fr>
				<nl>Wo</nl>
				<it>Mer</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>c39838d84fd81cbfeb7cf74ccd8ae9d0</id>
				<org>Weiter</org>
				<en>Next</en>
				<es>Más lejos</es>
				<fr>Plus loin</fr>
				<nl>Verder</nl>
				<it>Più avanti</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>6559ff591c6697998b4b2eb3c341e94c</id>
				<org>Weiter zur naechsten Seite</org>
				<en>Continue to next page</en>
				<es>Continuar a la página siguiente</es>
				<fr>Suite à la page suivante</fr>
				<nl>Doorgaan naar de volgende pagina</nl>
				<it>Continua alla pagina successiva</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>cdf47deb104473eb8905af1b49d1bfa8</id>
				<org>Zurück zur vorherigen Seite</org>
				<en>Back to previous page</en>
				<es>Volver a la página anterior</es>
				<fr>Retour à la page précédente</fr>
				<nl>Terug naar vorige pagina</nl>
				<it>Torna alla pagina precedente</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>3eff505aeeeb34636c24cbc862fa554f</id>
				<org>Angemeldet und Bezahlt</org>
				<en>Registered and paid</en>
				<es>Inscrito y pagado</es>
				<fr>Enregistrées et payées</fr>
				<nl>Ingeschreven en betaald</nl>
				<it>Registered and paid</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>70cddb2d45f04a29f54704ccb632e576</id>
				<org>Nur Angemeldet</org>
				<en>Just Registered</en>
				<es>Sólo registrados</es>
				<fr>Just Inscrits</fr>
				<nl>Just Geregistreerd</nl>
				<it>Just Registered</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>69566353ee20bf15bbfab86db1146ed6</id>
				<org>Frei</org>
				<en>Free</en>
				<es>Libre</es>
				<fr>Gratuit</fr>
				<nl>Vrij</nl>
				<it>Libero</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>f59c72aa1d236904f5ddbc69cd1b7b7b</id>
				<org>Bitte auswählen</org>
				<en>Please select</en>
				<es>Por favor seleccione</es>
				<fr>S&amp;#39;il vous plaît choisir</fr>
				<nl>Selecteer</nl>
				<it>Si prega di selezionare</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>f797991b3da9682b516352d95ab0b6d8</id>
				<org>Sehr schlecht</org>
				<en>Very bad</en>
				<es>Muy mal</es>
				<fr>Très mauvais</fr>
				<nl>Zeer slecht</nl>
				<it>Molto male</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>6a14cc29a33cb8ab42ba7884ce469ea8</id>
				<org>Sehr gut</org>
				<en>Very good</en>
				<es>Muy bueno</es>
				<fr>Très bon</fr>
				<nl>Erg goed</nl>
				<it>Molto buono</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id>1eb869cbc62e298e310d0b4d40ef819b</id>
				<org>Bewertung</org>
				<en>Rating</en>
				<es>Evaluación</es>
				<fr>Évaluation</fr>
				<nl>Beoordeling</nl>
				<it>Valutazione</it>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id></id>
				<org></org>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
			<entry>
				<id></id>
				<org></org>
				<file>System</file>
			</entry>
		</content>
	</table>
</lansuite>
